Okay, let's talk about how to do the front and back of the front of the front and back of the back when the waistline is broken.
We will give you a case of the lower back of the lower back.
When we get a new style, we must make a comparison with the original style.
When comparing with the original style, we will find that the A-shape is still retained, the B-shape is gone, which means it is eliminated.
Then the dragon-shaped throat is gone, but it adds a lower back.
So when we analyze this style, the B-shape must be eliminated first, and then I need to move the dragon-shaped throat to the lower back to form the lower back.
So first eliminate the B-shape, and then the B-shape is combined.
After combining, then determine the position of the new throat, and then divide the new throat and the dragon-shaped throat into two parts.
Then this is a small part, this is a part, and then we combine the dragon-shaped throat, and then open the new throat.
After opening,
After opening, then our new throat, in general, this woman's clothes, the chest and chest throat, the general situation of the throat, unless you make very harmonious clothes.
If you don't make very harmonious clothes, the throat will be a certain distance from the BP point, and then you shake and hot, it will form a natural, a full-fledged shape.
Okay, so finally we determine that our structure line is complete.
Okay, so now we change back to the 3D window.
First of all, we need to eliminate the B-throat, which is very similar to this type.
This type of sound is through the B-throat, so we must eliminate the B-throat first.
We will eliminate the B-throat according to what we said before, and then we will cut it off.
After cutting it off, we will delete the sound in the middle of this section.
Then click on the two lines and press the Shift key to select the two B-throat and the two throat strings.
Then we click on Merge, and then we merge them together.
Then we have a special tool for rotating the throat in Qo3D.
It needs to select the edge of the throat, but the edge of our throat is made up of two lines.
If you click on the two lines here and press the Shift key, and then select this one, the rotating throat will not appear.
It only appears when you select two identical lines.
After turning the throat, because you merged the B-throat, there is a small gap here.
This small gap is general.
When we draw the Xuelonggu line, we can draw it smoothly.
So how do we deal with it in Qo3D?
You can also lift it up.
For example, let's lift this point up.
After lifting it up, let this line form a straight line.
Then we delete the original B-throat throat.
After deleting it, we need a rotating throat tool.
It must be equal to the length of the two sides of the throat.
Let's take a look at it now.
It's not equal, it's almost 0.2 mm.
Okay, so let's adjust it and make it equal.
This side is 118.3.
Then this line, we choose this line.
Press the right mouse button to change the length.
We pay attention to the length of it.
Is to adjust this side.
The B-point of the throat is not moving.
So let's change it to the end.
Then also change to 118.3.
After changing, we press the Shift key to select two edges.
Press the left mouse button to select two edges of the throat.
Press the right mouse button to select two edges of the throat.
Then the rotating throat appears.
After the rotating throat appears,
Then we click on the position of the new throat.
Start to click.
The new throat position, we look at this style.
The style is a little bit below the night.
So our new throat position must be closer to the night.
Then this is the position of the new throat.
After selecting this point,
Then at this time,
We
New throat and long-haired throat.
Divide our circle into two pieces.
On the left, click on the end point again.
Divide into two pieces.
One piece is this small piece.
The other piece is the big blue one.
Okay, then we choose the mouse to move to this small piece.
Press the left mouse button.
Okay, then we drag the mouse.
Drag up, drag the mouse, rotate.
In this case, my long-haired throat will merge.
Then press the left mouse button again.
Press the left mouse button, it will move over.
Then at this time, we will see the position of the new throat.
The position of the new throat will come out at this time.
Okay, then the end point of the new throat.
That is, the position of the throat.
If we use the principle of rotation,
It should be on the BP point.
But in fact, when we are making clothes,
When it reaches the BP point,
It will form a very sharp shape of the chest.
Although the effect will be better after you sweat.
But it's not usually done like this.
It's a little bit distance.
A little bit farther.
One to two centimeters or so.
Okay, let's click on the left button at this position.
After clicking the left button,
Then at this time, our throat will come out directly.
So let's look at the edge of the throat.
It's completely the same.
There is also a throat.
So in this place of the A-throat,
We press the Shift key.
Then you can just cut it off.
Cut it off and throw it away.
Throw away the middle one.
Because of the rotation and processing of the throat,
Although we are symmetrical,
But this side didn't do it either.
So at this time, we need to draw an internal line.
Then cut it off.
After cutting it off, we delete this line.
After deleting it, we go back to the edit point and line tool.
Select the front center line.
Left click to select the front center line.
Right click to select the single mouse.
Align to open the edge seam line.
At this time, we will make a symmetrical style.
After that, we click on the virtual seam line.
We see that the throat automatically fits on the seam line.
The seam line is already there.
Let's put the A-throat together.
After that, let's look at the shoulder line.
Press the Shift key.
Then we merge the shoulder line.
Next, we merge the side seam line.
Okay, it's merged.
After merging,
Let's open the arrangement point.
Okay.
Let's check it again.
Okay, there's no problem.
Let's simulate.
Okay.
At this time, we look again.
I'm now, look at me.
I arranged two models.
The purpose of arranging two models is to let everyone take a closer look.
After I do the
chest rotation,
my shape,
the shape of the chest bulge,
and the one that has not been rotated,
or only keeps a breastplate,
such a shape is exactly the same.
This is what I said before.
The principle of chasing,
long-distance chasing,
or counter-chasing is the same.